Taylor Law

4168771234 • lawtinloklhl@gmail.com • https://jswildcards.github.io

Professional Summary

A software developer with 1-year professional experience in Hong Kong. Passionate about new technology, focus on implementation and enhancements of software products. He is currently looking for an entry-level software developer position in Toronto (in-person) / Canada (remote).

Work Experience

Software Developer

Landcrowd Limited (Spacious), Hong Kong

Feb 2022 - Jan 2023

- Maintained and developed new features for Spacious (https://www.spacious.hk), a real estate listing platform that allows agents and landlords to post their listings and receive enquiries from searchers using Ruby on Rails (w/ Sidekiq), TypeScript, SCSS, PostgreSQL, Docker, Git.
- Focused on enhancing the lister's experience while posting a new listing on the platform.
- Developed and maintained the process of creating a new listing, including payment processing, email notifications on successful/failed posting, frontend UI and logic, and backend logic.
- Managed the development of a listing management dashboard for listers, which allowed them to check their posted listings, expiration dates, and manage listing quotas for their company and agents.
- Managed background tasks, such as sending email notifications to listers at the right time when certain
 events occurred or processing bulk-upload listings from JSON-formatted files provided by agency
 companies.
- Handled backend logic, such as marking a listing as expired.
- Maintained database management by creating database migration when needed.
- Rewrote the blogsite (https://www.spacious.hk/en/blog) using WordPress, PHP, and CSS.

STEM Tutor

Coding 101, Hong Kong

Sept 2021 - Jan 2022

• Taught coding and robotic knowledge, such as Python, Micro:bit, Arduino, IoT, Microsoft MakeCode Arcade, to primary and secondary students

Education

BSc Computer Science

City University of Hong Kong

Sept 2019 - Jul 2021

Higher Diploma in Software Engineering

Institute of Vocational Education Hong Kong

Sept 2017 - Jul 2019

Skill

Ruby on Rails, ReactJS, Typescript, HTML/CSS, Java, Node.js, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Docker, Git **Languages:** English, Mandarin, Cantonese

Activity and Award

Winner of Web Design & Development Section

WorldSkills Hong Kong Competition 2018

2018

- Gained a position of Top 3
- Represented Hong Kong Team to participate in the 10th Guangzhou / Hong Kong / Macau / Chengdu Youth Skills Competition 2018 Web Design & Development Section